mybidmonster.com.ng 2015-12-23

# Privacy | shopandmall.com.ng

### **Introduction**

Our privacy policy shows our commitment and dedication to protect your privacy. The statements describes the ways in which we collect, store, use and protect your personal information and it is important for you to review this privacy policy. By "personal information" we mean information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider anonymous information to constitute personal information as it cannot be used to identify a specific person. shopandmall.com.ng and its affiliates.

By providing shopandmall.com.ng and its affiliates with your personal information you expressly consent to us processing your personal information in accordance with the terms of our privacy policy. We may amend our privacy policy at any time by posting a revised version on shopandmall.com.ng and its affiliates sites. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it and, following such posting, your continued use of shopandmall.com.ng , your customer account (Customer Account) and the related tools and services on our sites shall constitute your express consent to us continuing to process your personal information in accordance with the terms of our revised privacy policy.

We would encourage you to check Mybidmonster regularly for the most up-to-date version of our privacy policy. If we are going to use your personal information in any way other than the way set out in our privacy policy, we will notify you via email and you will have the choice of whether or not to allow us to use your personal information in such a way.

###   
Our collection and management of your personal information

In order to register/join and start using the shopandmall.com.ng, you will be asked to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your date of birth, address, email address and telephone number and other identifying information which we may combine with your personal information. Additionally, in order for us to verify your identity we may request from you valid proof of identification in the form of a copy of your passport, certificate of registration, your resident's visa/permit, your national ID card and/or your driver's license.

You should ensure that the email address you have registered with us is always up-to-date so that we can always contact you with important information regarding your use of our site and services. We may also need to collect selected financial information from you, such as your credit card and/or bank account details.

Your Internet protocol (or IP) address (which is a unique number assigned to your computer server or your Internet service provider (or ISP), information about your computer (for example, browser type) and navigation information (for example, the pages you visit on shopandmall.com.ng and its affiliates) along with the times you access **our sites** may also be tracked against your personal information for the purposes of preventing fraud, to improve our services to you and, more generally, better manage our users' use of shopandmall.com.ng and its affiliated sites. Finally, we may collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, we may collect information related to your contact with our customer support team or store the results when you respond to a survey.

### **How we use your personal information.**

We use your personal information to provide and improve our services to you. We may also use your personal information to prevent illegal activities and implement our User Agreement with you. For example, we may share some of the personal information you give us with banks (for example, to comply with our anti-money laundering obligations), to credit card authorization, processing and verification services or for fraud screening purposes.

### Children's Privacy

This Web site is designed for an adult audience only, and children should not use this Web site. We will not intentionally collect online any personal information (such as a child's name or e-mail address) from children under the age of 18. If you think that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 18, please contact us and we will address the issue.We may need, in such circumstances, to request proof of identification from you (e.g. in the form of a copy of your passport or national ID). These entities may not use your personal information for any other secondary purposes beyond the purpose for which your personal information was provided to them by us, unless they are required to do so by law.

shopandmall.com.ng and its affiliates may offer a service called "Tell a Friend" that allows you to notify friends about open auctions and our services. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We do not save or share such information and email address, they are only used for this one time mailing. Please note, however, that shopandmall.com.ng and its affiliates oppose the practice of sending unsolicited commercial emails, also known as "spam". Therefore, we request that you send "Tell A Friend" emails only to people known by you who may be interested in the auction. If someone asks you not to send these emails to him or her, please comply.

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose your personal information to law enforcement agencies, government agencies or other third parties where we are compelled to by court order or similar legal procedure; where we are required so to do to comply with law; where we are cooperating with an ongoing law enforcement investigation; or where we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity or to investigate a possible violation of our User Agreement. In the event of the sale of shopandmall.com.ng its affiliates, subsidiaries or any assets of the business, your personal information may be disclosed to a potential purchaser for the purposes of the continued provision of the service to you. Otherwise, we will only disclose your personal information to a third party with your permission. We do not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties in the normal course of doing business and will only share your personal information with third parties in accordance with this privacy policy.

### How to Access, review and amend your personal information

You can access and review your information under "Profile/MYCP" and preference when you log into your Customer Account on shopandmall.com.ng and its affiliates. If your personal information changes in any way, if it is incorrectly presented in your Customer Account or if you wish to amend it for any other reason, you should promptly update, amend or correct your personal information (as applicable) by logging into the shopandmall.com.ng and its affiliates websites. Additionally, in order to deactivate your Customer Account you will need to contact our customer support team via shopandmall.com.ng and its affiliates. Following the deactivation of your Customer Account we may need to retain your personal information to comply with law, for technical troubleshooting requirements, to prevent fraud, assist in any legal investigations and take any other actions otherwise permitted by law.  

### How we communications with you.

Upon registering your Customer Account you will receive an email requesting that you confirm your registration and confirming your successful registration. Once registered, you may occasionally receive information on products, services and special deals from us. We offer you the option of either receiving or not receiving such information when you register. Should you wish to change the option you chose on registration you can do so at any time in your Customer Account Profile/MyCP or through the preference tab.

Third party website links. shopandmall.com.ng and its affiliates may contain links to other websites. shopandmall.com.ng has no control over the practices of these other websites and is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage you, when you leave shopandmall.com.ng and its affiliates, to read the privacy statements of each and every website you visit if you intend to provide personal information to such website.

### About Cookies.

"Cookies" are pieces of information that are passed to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. shopandmall.com.ng uses cookies to recognize repeat visitors, to automatically enter your login ID in our bid form, and to provide additional features to make bidding & buying at our sites easier and more efficient. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can turn them off using your browser's settings. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you. Cookies help us improve your experience of shopandmall.com.ng and also help us understand which parts of sites are the most popular.

### Our Competition Offerings

Competitions may be made available on shopandmall.com.ng from time to time. You do not have to participate in these, however, if you choose to, you may be asked to disclose some personal information. This privacy policy will apply to any personal information disclosed by you in relation to any such competition on shopandmall.com.ng. At the time of entering the competition, it will be made clear to you who will have access to your personal information and the reasons for such access. You are, of course, not obliged to continue with your competition entry if you do not wish to disclose the requested personal information. 

### **How we protect your personal information**

We hold your personal information on servers. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer of your personal information to, and the storage of that personal information on our servers. We take reasonable measures to safeguard all your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, including the use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology with high security Supports 128- and 256-bit encryption, certified by **DigiCert**. Never share your username and password or any details about your Customer Account with anyone. If you are concerned that your username, password or Customer Account has been compromised, please contact our customer support team immediately. In particular, if you are concerned that your password has been compromised, please ensure you change your password immediately by logging onto shopandmall.com.ng. ****

### **Protecting your login ID and password  **                                                                                                     

Always keep your shopandmall.com.ng account username and password secret. They are your only identification for bidding purposes. If you receive information about a bid you did not place, or questionable communications regarding your account, please contact shopandmall.com.ng Customer Support immediately by email. One potential way for someone to steal your login ID and password is if you bookmark any area on MYCP or a bid submission page. ****

### About SSL, security, and firewall problems                                                                                                 

Some older browsers (such as IE 3.0.2) have known SSL bugs. These can result in the browser crashing on SSL pages, compromise on security or giving error messages. We recommend that you upgrade to the latest version of whatever browser you prefer. For users behind corporate firewalls, you need to configure your web browser security settings. This includes setting https or secure proxy settings. To determine if you have such a security problem, you can edit a secure URL, replacing 'https' (secure) with 'http' (insecure). If the page works with http:// but not https://, then you have a problem with your security settings. You should contact your system administrator for assistance. ****

### How your information is encrypted                                                                                                               

There are certain areas on the site where you may enter and submit additional information. Certain of these areas are encrypted using SSL encrypted transmissions between your Web browser and our Web server. This is designed to reduce the chance that someone (e.g. on your network at work or at your Internet service provider) may try to compromise your private information as it travels from your Web browser to our secure server. You'll know when transmitted data is encrypted by a security notice when you enter an encrypted page, and by the presence of an icon on your browser, either a key for Netscape or a lock for Microsoft Internet Explorer. The pages where you submit your account information, place a bid, and receive confirmation of a successful bid are all encrypted. In addition, your credit card information is encrypted within the shopandmall.com.ng database and access to such information is restricted. This system is unique and designed to provide you with additional security when purchasing items on shopandmall.com.ng. ****

### How you can contact us about privacy questions

We reserve the right to repeat comments about our products made in communications with us for marketing purposes.

### Prohibited items

Below is a list of prohibited items that cannot be listed on MyBidMonster  
Alcohol  
Animals and wildlife products – examples include live animals, mounted specimens, and ivory  
Artifacts, grave-related items, and Native American arts and crafts  
Catalytic converters and test pipes  
Charity or fundraising listings  
Contracts  
Counterfeit currency and stamps  
Credit cards  
Currency selling  
Drugs and drug paraphernalia  
Drugs, describing drugs or drug-like substances  
Event tickets  
Firearms, weapons, and knives – examples include pepper spray, replicas, and stun guns (see also military items)  
Food and healthcare items  
Gift cards  
Government documents, IDs, and licenses  
Hazardous materials – examples include batteries, fireworks, and Freon  
Human parts and remains  
Items encouraging illegal activity – examples include an eBook describing how to create methamphetamine  
Lottery tickets  
Mailing lists and personal information  
Manufacturers' coupons  
Medical devices – examples include contact lenses, pacemakers, and surgical instruments  
Military related items including firearms, weapons, and knives                           
Multi-level marketing, pyramid, and matrix programs  
Offensive material – examples include ethnically or racially offensive material and Nazi memorabilia  
Pesticides  
Pirated materials like CDs and DVDs  
Pirated software  
Plants and seeds                            
Police-related items  
Political memorabilia (reproduction)  
Postage meters  
Prescription drugs  
Prohibited services  
Recalled items  
Slot machines  
Stolen property and property with removed serial numbers  
Surveillance equipment  
Travel  
Weeds (see plants and seeds)  
We reserve the right to add to this list at anytime.

### How you can contact us

If you have any questions about our privacy policy please   or write to:

**Nigeria: Bidmonster Online Trading** **.**

#### 22 Oweh Street,  
Jobowu,  
Lagos, Nigeria.

#### To make enquiries about our services, seek assistance, give feedback and more information please [Contact](http://www.shopandmall.com.ng/main-contact) us through this link.
